Rohan Jariwala

Montreal, QC, H3H-IK4 · 438-924-7117 · rohanjariwala 03@gmail.com

PROFILE

PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/rohanjariwala03

http://rohanjariwala.com/#/

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Personable Lead Software Developer accustomed to heading up successful development teams through agile direction and careful delegation. Willing to work with multinational companies and achieve the goals of company, rings both cutting-edge programming expertise and exceptional interpersonal skills to leadership roles.

SKILLS

- In-depth understanding of computer programming language and ability to code.
- Knowledge of most types of graphic design software, including object oriented management and metadata management software.
- Active listening skills to truly hear feedback and incorporate notes effectively.

- Ability to think creatively and find unique solutions to problems.
- Strong communication skills to effectively speak with people at any level of an organization.
- Proficient with languages such as Dart, Java, C, C#. C++, and many more.

EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Developer, 11/2021 to Current

Categen Inc. - Montreal, Quebec

- o Collaborated on stages of systems development lifecycle from requirement gathering to production releases.
- O Developed software for both desktop and mobile operating systems.
- Collaborated with CTO to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on prerelease software project development.
- Hire new developers for the company and lead those towards the success of the company.
- O Working with Flutter, Dart, Api, Local Database as well as server side database, websocket and many more things to improve software and applications for my workplace.
- Working with native android and deploying apps on play store and App Store through CI/Cd.

Software Developer, 07/2019 to 05/2020

TechDeveloper - Surat, Gujarat

- o Planned and developed interfaces that simplified overall system and offered ease of use.
- Translated verbal customer requirements into written use cases and testable development stories.
- o Led version control efforts for organization, employing GitHub and other public and open source repositories.
- o Implemented target tracking to research prototypes over large data sets.
- o Developed Applications in native android with java and Kotlin and as well worked with flutter to developed cross platform applications.

Software Developer, 05/2017 to 06/2019

TechDeveloper - Surat, Gujarat

- O Started as a Intern in college campus and worked for more than 1 year.
- o Learned Java and worked on some new projects through out my career in C.B.Patel.
- o Worked with api integration and Java advance for software development.
- o Aquire knowledge about Mean(Mongo Db, Express, Angular, Node Js.) stack technology.

EDUCATION

PG in Mobile Application And Development: Computer Science, 08/2021 Cegep De La Gaspesie et des Iles - Montreal, QC

Bachelor in Computer Application: Computer Science, 06/2019 C.B,Patel Computer College - Surat, GJ

REFERENCES

Hieu Doan - CEO, Categen Inc. +1 (514) 813-2603

Nigel Yong - CTO, Categen Inc. +1 (438) 223-3900

Gianluca - CEO, Indera Technologies. +1 (647) 802-8573